{
    "kind": "dragndrop",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M1L4a.json",
            "kind": "draganddrop",
            "Instruccion": "Connect the two parts of the sentences ",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She went to the mall",
                    "answer": "because she wanted a dvd"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She got good grades",
                    "answer": "because she worked hard."
                },
                {
                    "question": "She couldn't go to school yesterday",
                    "answer": "because she was sick"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She loves visiting her grandparents",
                    "answer": "because they have a large yard"
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ate three sandwiches",
                    "answer": "because she was very hungry"
                },
                {
                    "question": "",
                    "answer": ""
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M1L4a.json",
            "kind": "draganddrop",
            "Instruccion": "Read and match",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He has a sore throat.",
                    "answer": "He should drink lemon juice and honey."
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has a broken arm.",
                    "answer": "His mom should take him to the hospital."
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has a stomachache.",
                    "answer": "He shouldn't eat so much chocolate."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M4L19a.json",
            "kind": "draganddrop",
            "Instruccion": "Read and match",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We use the past simple to talk about",
                    "answer": "experiences at some time in our lives up to now."
                },
                {
                    "question": "We use the present perfect to talk about",
                    "answer": "finished actions that happened in the past. "
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP5M5L24a.json",
            "kind": "draganddrop",
            "Instruccion": "Match the questions and answers",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "And what was Pele doing?",
                    "answer": "He was barking at the bottom of the tree."
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did you do? ",
                    "answer": "I put his leash on and tied him to another tree."
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}